{
    "id": "191555a5e2b845cd80a20441dfeffb30",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who is this present ………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am really angry ……………. you.",
            "description": "With is used after a number of adjectives which say how people are feeling towards others.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………… all this work to do, I won’t have time to take a holiday.",
            "description": "With can introduce the accompanying circumstances.",
            "answers": [
                "With",
                "For",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was talking ……………. such a low voice that I could not hear anything.",
            "description": "We say ‘in a voice’.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If we go …………… car, we will reach there before sunset.",
            "description": "We use 'by' with car, train, bus etc.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The actress has always been very nice ……………. her fans.",
            "description": "Words like kind, nice, polite and rude are followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….friends like you, who needs enemies?",
            "description": "With can mean 'because there are/is.'",
            "answers": [
                "With",
                "Without",
                "For",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of movies are you interested …………..?",
            "description": "We say 'interested in something'.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The cottage is pleasant to live …………….",
            "description": "We 'live in' a cottage or a house. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which flight is she travelling ……………?",
            "description": "People travel 'on a flight'",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You are the only woman I have ever been in love…………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That is what I am afraid ……………..",
            "description": "We say 'afraid of something'.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}